mediahub.com 2016-06-06

# Our Digital Story, Developing For Over 5 Years

**March 2012**

This Privacy Policy covers MEDIAHUB.COM ("MEDIAHUB.COM" "our" "website") in relation to visitors and customers including advertisers and publishers.

This is our official Privacy Policy which forms part of your legal agreement with us UNDER OUR TERMS OF USE. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to be sure you understand how we collect and use information and under what circumstances we share information about you.

Any terms not defined in this Privacy Policy are defined in our Terms of Use.

### Data

When you visit MEDIAHUB.COM and use our services an insertion order will be completed and electronically signed with company information and personal information such as: Name, Company Name, Mailing Address, Email Address, Phone Number, Basic Site Information (URL, Channel, Impression Traffic). In addition, if you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

Further, when you use our Website, we often use third party operational service providers and technology that can recognize, collect and transmit information that is associated with you or your computer and browser, but which does not personally identify you. Although the term "cookie" commonly is used to refer to a small text file stored on a computer that keeps track of your visits to web sites and/or can contain log-in information so you don’t have to re-enter information each time you visit, we will use the term "cookie" to refer generically to any technology that can recognize, collect or transmit information about your visits to our Websites. "Cookie" information typically includes such data as the Internet or web domain that referred you, the type of operating system and browser you are using, the date and time of your visit, information relating to activities on our Websites (e.g., ‘clickstream’ data) and other technical attributes of your visits to our Website. No personally identifiable information is collected by this process and we use the information collected through cookies to analyze trends, administer our Websites, track movements on our Website and gather aggregate demographic information about visitors so we can continually improve our Website.

Cookies store information that allows our Website to recognize a users’ computer or access device each time it is used to visit our Website and cookies can keep count of how often you return to our Website. Cookies can also track how you use our Website, your preferences for features and functions and can store information such as your log-in information, so you don’t have to re-enter them each time you return to our Website. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer for purposes that are unrelated to our Website or your interaction with our Website.

You may stop or restrict cookies on your computer or purge them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences and you should consult the operating instructions that apply to your browser for instructions should you wish to do so and in general to determine how best to configure your browser settings to meet your requirements. Note that if you ‘turn off,’ purge or disable cookies, although you may still use our Website, you may not be able to use all of the features, functions or services available on our Website.

Similar to other commercial websites, we collect information to better serve the customer/visitor during their visit to MEDIAHUB.COM. Information may include: IP address, domain, browser type and language, referring website addresses, date/time of visits, page view data, and search keywords. This information is collected using the following standard web technologies:

When you visit MEDIAHUB.COM, we send one or more cookies to your computer. Cookies are used to improve the quality of our service. MEDIAHUB.COM also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage advertisements.

"Cookies" as indicated are data files, which often include an anonymous unique identifier, sent to your browser from a website. Cookies can only be read by the party placing the cookie, they cannot erase or alter any of your data and when used in the context of collecting this information, they do not include personal data.

"Log files" track actions occurring on Sites and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, click data and types of advertisements viewed.

"Web beacons" are electronic files used to track your navigation of a website or collection of sites, the completion of transactions, submittal of applications and browsing behavior.

Collectively these technologies enable us to better understand and segment our customers’ audiences on an aggregate basis. Data for targeting purposes is retained for up to 13 months after which time this data is deleted.

### How We Use The Information

MEDIAHUB.COM uses personal information such as email address, name and phone number for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers.

MEDIAHUB.COM may also use the information collected to notify you about important changes to our website, new services and special opportunities we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by contacting us at info@Mediahub.com

### Sharing Your Information

We do not collect personal or company information except when provided voluntarily by visitors to our website for the purpose of using the service. We do not rent, sell or disseminate this information to third parties for promotional purposes without consent. We will only share this voluntarily-provided information to enable third party service providers to assist or facilitate in the services we provide; to comply with applicable laws and regulations or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; to enforce an agreement or to protect our rights; with any parent, affiliated or successor entity; in connection with any asset sale, transfer, divestiture or liquidation; in connection with strategic alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements to permit the offering of products or services we think may be of interest to you or where we have determined that the information will be used in a responsible manner by the third party; or as permitted under any agreement with you.

Further, Mediahub only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of MEDIAHUB.COM in the specific circumstances:

> We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of use, including investigation of potential violations, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of MEDIAHUB.COM, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We also reserve the right to make your Personal Information available:

  * When compelled by a governmental agency, law, regulation, a court or other legal process;
  * If we believe you are, have or may violate any law, regulation or our Terms of Use;
  * If we believe you are or may be a threat to safety, security, property, interests or rights of us or anyone else;
  * In order to investigate, respond to or resolve problems or inquiries or protect, enforce or defend our rights, assets and/or interests;
  * In a merger, acquisition, change of control, joint venture or other business combination.

### Security

We use appropriate measures to ensure the security of all information, including the use of passwords, firewalls, encryption and remote servers, and routinely evaluate our practices to identify security threats or opportunities for the improvement of our services. No transmission of information is guaranteed to be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise data security. You acknowledge and agree to assume this risk when communicating with us.

As you may appreciate, the Internet is a public network of networks and we cannot guarantee that communications between you and MEDIAHUB.COM or others, through or from our Website, will be free from unauthorized access or interference by third parties such as hackers. By using our Website, you are agreeing to assume this risk and any and all responsibility and liability that may arise. That said, the security of your Personal Information is important to us and when possible we attempt to provide secure transmissions by using encryption software. We have also put in place reasonable physical, electronic and operational procedures to safeguard information and we limit access to your Personal Information to only those employees who need access in order to perform their duties.

### Changes

By using our website forms, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### Third Party Websites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or applications (including widgets) linked to or from our website nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our website. Please remember that your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies.

### Contact

Should you have questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please contact a MEDIAHUB.COM representative ( [info@mediahub.com](mailto:info@mediahub.com)) .
